周四早上6:28
早上好
Good morning.
几点了
What time is it?
6点28
6:28.
你应该在睡觉的  但我很开心你没有睡觉
You should be asleep, but I'm glad you're not.
你的术后病理报告和核磁共振结果出来了
Your post-op pathology and MRI results are finally in, and...
很好
they're good.
特别好
Very good.
这个暂停是为了戏剧效果吗
Was the pause for dramatic effect?
是的
Yes.
手术很成功
The surgery was a success.
现在你只需要休息就好
The only thing you need now is rest.
还有放化疗
And chemo and radiation.
你一整晚都在这吗
Have you been here all night?
我在化验室的椅子上睡的
I slept in a chair in the lab.
你应该回家睡觉
Well, you should go home and go to sleep.
我不能回家
I can't go home.
还有31分钟我就要上班了
My next shift starts in 31 minutes.
手术很成功
The surgery was a success.
BGM: Walking On Sunshine by Katrina And The Waves
♪ I used to think maybe you loved me ♪
♪ Now, baby, I'm sure ♪
♪ And I just can't wait till the day when you knock on my door ♪
♪ Now I'm walking on sunshine ♪
♪ I'm walking on sunshine ♪
莉亚
我们今天能谈谈吗
删除信息
删除
♪ And don't it feel good? ♪
♪ Hey, all right, now ♪
手术很成功
The surgery was a success.
格拉斯曼医生现在只需要休息
All Dr. Glassman needs now is rest.
真是好消息
That's great news.
还有放化疗
And chemo and radiation.
你怎么样
How are you?
我不需要休息
I don't need rest.
我在一把很舒服的椅子上睡过了
I fell asleep in a comfortable chair.
很好  有人扰乱了值班表
Good. Someone screwed up the on-call schedule
急诊现在缺人
and left the ER short-staffed.
我需要两个人顶上去
I need two volunteers to fill in.
好消息是不会被我盯着
Good news is you won't have me breathing down your neck.
坏消息是要值36小时的班
Bad news is it's a 36-hour shift.
弹性工作新政策真是太荒唐了
This new flex-time policy is ridiculous.
我们的薪水还不够低吗
Aren't our salaries low enough already?
不是钱的问题
It's not about the money.
安德鲁斯认为医生即便累得不行
Andrews believes that surgeons need to be at their best
也要保持最佳状态
even when they're exhausted.
住院医师学习的唯一办法就是去做
The only way for residents to learn it is to do it.
得拿出比赛的劲来练习
You got to practice like you play.
不睡觉的话你也做不到
And you can't do either without sleep.
你可以随时去和安德鲁斯理论
You're free to take it up with Andrews any time.
一到五之间挑一个数
Pick a number between one and five.
2.5
2.5.
-一  -那不是之间
- One. - That's not between...
-五  -三
- Five. - Three.
该死
Aw, damn it.
好消息
Good news.
梅伦德斯医生不会盯着我们
Dr. Melendez won't be breathing down our necks.
36小时值班开始
你们都是第二年住院医师
You're second-year residents.
这是证明你们不再需要
This is a great opportunity for you to prove
被人盯着的绝佳时机
that you don't need a babysitter anymore.
我今天有一大堆自己的事要处理
And I have a ton of personal crap I got to take care of today,
所以我值班
so I'm on call,
但不是急事就不要找我了
but don't call me unless you absolutely need to,
最好不要找我
but you better not need to.
心肌梗塞病人在一区  股骨复合骨折在二区
You've got a M.I. in one and compound femur in two.
我要杀了那混蛋
I'm gonna kill that bastard!
他死定了
He's dead!
流血的疯醉汉在五区
And a bleeding, angry drunk guy in five.
把你的手拿开
Get your hands off of me!
你他妈在看什么
What the hell are you looking at?!
良     医
第二季  第三集
切除子病变的宫内膜大约只需要一小时
Excising the endometrial lesions should only take about an hour.
我们会通过你肚脐眼处的单切口做手术
We'll be operating through a single incision in your belly button.
你甚至都看不到伤疤
You won't even be able to see the scar.
你们怎么通过这么小的切口做手术
How can you operate through such a small opening?
是一项新的技术  把单切口
It's a new technique using a single port
分成几部分  方便镜头和工具操作
divided into sections for the camera and our tools.
-新的  -对他们而已
- New? - To them.
别担心  对我来说不是
Don't worry. It isn't to me.
我有信心可以缓解你的疼痛
I'm confident that this will resolve your pain
治好不孕
and infertility issues.
谢谢你  谢谢你们
Thank you, all of you.
做母亲是我唯一的愿望
Being a mother is all I've ever wanted.
我们第一次约会时
On our first date,
她就跟我说了想好的孩子的名字
she told me the baby's name she'd picked out.
当时才17岁
We were 17.
说来听听
So let's hear 'em.
男孩叫杰克逊  女孩叫卡梅伦
Jackson for a boy and Cameron for a girl.
很好  我喜欢这两个名字
Very nice. I like them.
我也是
So do I.
你很快就会成为一名很棒的母亲了
And you are going to be an amazing mother very soon.
给她做准备吧
Let's get her prepped.
我以为是因为她太漂亮了
I thought it was just because she was so pretty and, uh,
有一阵子了
it had been a while,
但她离开后  还是这样
but after she left, it stayed.
你觉得她给我下了伟哥吗
You think she roofied me with Viagra?
当然  那也是可能的
Sure. That could have happened.
或者是酒精
Or maybe it was the alcohol,
大麻以及事前磕的摇头丸
marijuana, and Molly you pre-gamed with.
有很多种不同的药会导致阴茎异常勃起
A lot of different drugs can cause priapism.
尤其是在车库里造的假药
Especially those cooked up in a garage.
我能碰吗
Is it okay if I touch it?
好吧
Okay.
阴茎海绵体僵硬  腺体松弛
Rigid corpora cavernosa and flaccid glands.
那是什么意思  她说什么
What's that mean? What's she getting?
已经超过四个小时了
It's been over four hours.
你不想它坏死
You don't want necrosis to set in.
坏死  你是说我的...  我的小弟弟会死
N-Necrosis? Are you saying that my... My penis could die?
可能  但不会  因为我们得赶紧的
It could, but it won't because we're going to move fast.
你们准备怎么做
What the hell are you going to do with that?
我们要排走缺氧的血  恢复血液循环
We need to remove the deoxygenated blood to restore circulation.
你会有一点点挤压感
You're going to feel a small pinch and then some pressure.
她在撒谎吗
Is she lying?
我不确定
I'm not sure.
天啊  疼死我了
Holy mother of God, that hurts!
我就出去散了会儿步  想清净一下
I go out for a short walk so I can have one moment of peace,
回家就看到这样的情况
and this is what I come home to.
怎么了
What's the problem?
他的嘴显然大到能塞进灯泡
His mouth was obviously big enough to get it in.
他肯定拉伤了咬肌
He must have strained his masseter.
痉挛导致牙关紧闭
It's gone into spasm and caused lockjaw.
给他打针镇定剂  用开口器械撬开
So give him a sedative and pry it open with a McIvor.
我试过了  撬不开
I tried. It won't budge.
他说痛得...
And he said it hurt like a son of a...
伊内兹
Inez.
他就是那么说的
That's what he said.
我放了个牙垫  但我不知道...
I put in a bite block, but I don't know...
叫利姆过来
Call Lim.
我们应该证明能独立处理病情
We're supposed to be proving our independence.
我用开口器械再试一次
I will try again with the McIvor.
可千万别撕裂了咬肌
You don't want to tear the masseter.
如果牙垫滑落  他猛地闭上嘴
If the bite block slips and he gags,
灯泡就会碎掉  碎片会被吸入肺部
he will have broken glass and vomit in his lungs.
我可以麻醉他
I could put him under.
如有必要  可以把他的下巴错位
Then I can dislocate his jaw if I have to.
没有利姆在  我们绝对不能那么做
We definitely can't do that without calling Lim.
也是
That's true.
我希望别打扰她干大事
I hope we don't interrupt anything important.
别担心  她不是在睡觉就是在洗衣服
Don't worry. She's either sleeping or doing laundry.
她的生活过得挺无趣的
There's nothing interesting going on in her life.
无罪
Not guilty.
你有什么反驳驾校的话吗  女士
Do you have something against traffic school, ma'am?
法官阁下  被告已经没资格上驾校了
Your Honor, the defendant's not eligible for traffic school.
去年她已经违反交规三次
This is her third moving violation in the last year.
只是疑似违规  非常感谢
Alleged violation, thank you very much.
骑摩托开每小时160公里
Traveling 100 miles per hour on a motorcycle?
你是找死吗
Do you have a death wish?
我完全没开到160
I wasn't going anywhere near 100.
那你当时开多快
So how fast were you going?
好问题
Excellent question.
我确定给我开罚单的警察
And one I assure you the officer who issued my ticket
也不能回答这个问题
will not be able to answer.
加州交通法规定
California State Vehicle Code mandates
所有激光雷达测速装置必须校准
that all LIDAR speed-measurement devices be calibrated...
至少
at least once a...
抱歉  我需要接这个电话
Sorry, I need to get this.
不  你需要关机
No, you need to turn it off.
法官阁下  我是圣文德医院的创伤外科医生
Your Honor, I'm a trauma surgeon at St. Bonaventure,
现在该我值班  所以
and I'm on call, so...
五分钟
Five minutes.
暂时休庭五分钟
The court is adjourned for a five-minute recess.
我不是说得很明白吗
I thought I was clear.
你们独立解决不了的问题我才会帮你们
I'm available to help with stuff you can't do on your own.
电影《亚当斯一家》的人物  用灯泡变过小把戏
小肥达叔叔可不算在内
Uncle Fester Jr. does not qualify.
中午12:18  值班5小时18分
我认为这种状况下应该对他进行全麻
I think the situation warrants putting him under a general an...
然后把他下巴弄错位吗  他又不是蛇
And dislocating his jaw? He's not a damn snake.
那我们该怎么办
So, what should we do?
向我证明你们和我想的一样有能力
Prove to me you're as capable as I think you are.
这没有道理
It doesn't make any sense.
全西海岸就我们医院尚未施行
We are the only hospital on the West Coast
研究生医学教育鉴定委员会关于
that hasn't adopted the ACGME mandate
实习医生值班不超过24小时的规定
on a 24-hour max shift length.
无数研究表明缺少睡眠对于
And numerous studies have shown the negative effects
批判性思维的负面影响
that sleep deprivation has on critical thinking,
会导致住院医生犯错误
which can cause residents to make mistakes
不仅对病患不利  也浪费金钱
that not only harm patients, but that waste money.
你看了不少东西
You've done your homework.
这件事我已经思考很久了
Um, it's something I've been thinking about for a long time.
在医学院我其实还就此写了篇论文
I actually did a paper on it at med school.
布朗医生  我也想过这点
Well, Dr. Browne, I've also thought about it.
其实当研究生医学教育鉴定委员会新规出台时
In fact, when the new ACGME guidelines were released,
我参加了一项分析弹性工作制的全国研究
I joined a nationwide study analyzing a flextime schedule.
发现只要满足每周工作不超过80小时
It found that as long as a weekly max of 80 hours is adhered to,
病患诊疗结果和住院医满意度
patient outcomes and resident satisfaction scores are better
都比每日规定最大值班量要好
than at hospitals with a daily max.
所以我们只需要同意或不同意
So we're just going to have to agree to disagree
我愚蠢的新政策是否「毫无道理」
about whether my foolish new policies "Make any sense."
不是  我没说
No, I didn't say...
我知道我告诉过你要再自信点
And I know I told you to be more assertive.
但你也要确保不要为此
But you also need to make sure that you don't forsake
舍弃你平常的优秀判断力
your normally excellent judgment in that effort.
-无论  -不好意思  抱歉
- Whether... - Excuse me. Yeah, hi, I'm sorry.
-我回来了  -好吧
- I'm back. - How wonderful.
找位置坐下等轮到你的案子吧
Take a seat until your case is called.
已经轮到我的案子了
Oh, my case was called.
你说过我可以休息五分钟
You said I could have a five-minute break.
法庭已经休庭五分钟了
The court took a five-minute break.
可你要休息很长一段时间
Yours is going to be considerably longer.
继续
Continue.
用11号刀切一个刺伤创口
Make a stab incision with an 11 blade,
我来插气腹针
and I'll insert the Veress.
他不会放心上的  别担心
He'll get over it. Don't worry.
安德鲁斯就喜欢时不时打击一下
Andrews just likes to hammer a nail every now and then.
我没有说他愚蠢
I didn't call him a fool.
我只是说他的规定毫无道理
I just said his policy didn't make sense.
注气完毕
Insufflation's complete.
可以用多端口了
Ready for the multi-port.
你说它毫无道理
You said it didn't make sense,
然后他解释说在他看来有道理
and he explained that in his opinion it did.
哪里有问题了
What's the problem?
问题是男人告诉女人应该自信点
The problem is men who tell women to be assertive,
一旦我们自信了  他们又批判我们
then as soon as we are, they criticize us for it.
我们倒成了贱人
We're the bitch.
你没叫他蠢蛋  他也没说你是贱人
You didn't call him a fool. He didn't call you a bitch.
没当面说
Not to her face.
他只是建议她应该说话措辞更谨慎
He just suggested she choose her words more carefully.
所以女人就得又有自信又谨慎吗
So, women have to be assertive but careful?
当你和老大说话时  对  大家都这样
When you're talking to your boss, yes. Everyone does.
如果你们辩论完了
If you're all done debating,
那来帮帮我这个老大吧
this boss could use some help.
你看到那个了吗
You see that?
她的卵巢上有病变
There are lesions on her ovary.
以前在影像上看不到
That wasn't visible on the imaging.
很小
It's small.
我们不损伤卵巢就可以切除  但是
We can excise it without damaging the ovary, but...
还有别的
there are others.
她的腹腔  膀胱  子宫
Her bowel, bladder, uterus.
难怪她会如此疼痛
No wonder she's been in so much pain.
我们从输卵管病变开始
We'll start with the Fallopian lesions
然后一个一个来
just go one by one.
布朗  我需要你刷手出去通知丈夫
Browne, I need you to scrub out and brief the husband.
解释子宫内膜异位比我们想象的严重得多
Explain the endometriosis is way more severe than we thought.
为什么是我  不是朴
Why me? Why not Park?
因为我认为你更擅长应对焦虑的亲属
Because I think you're better at talking to anxious relatives.
有什么问题吗
Is there a problem?
没有
No.
拉紧那片组织
Retract that tissue.
她今天怎么一点就炸
Why is she so on edge today?
不知道
No idea.
总有那么几天
Just one of those days.
不是指来月经那几天
I didn't mean one of "Those" days.
我是说人总有那么几天心情不爽快
I just meant, people wake up on the wrong side of the bed sometimes.
布朗医生解释过她为什么烦躁
Dr. Browne explained exactly why she was "On edge."
你是已经忘了
Did you forget already,
还是你压根就没听
or were you just not listening to begin with?
我又怎么了
Excuse me?
我们还是少说点话
We should cut back on the conversation
专心手术吧
and focus on the procedure.
我同意
I agree.
我想见她
I want to see her.
抱歉  你不能进入手术室
I'm sorry. You can't go into the OR.
我  我就从窗外看看  求你了
I'll just... I'll just look through the window, please.
丹尼尔  相信我
Daniel, trust me.
看到你美丽的妻子躺在手术台上
Seeing your beautiful wife on the operating table
不会减少你的焦虑
is not gonna make you less anxious.
一切都在掌控之中
Everything is under control.
唯一有变的
The only thing that's changed
就是手术时间长了
is how long the surgery's gonna take.
很抱歉
Look, I'm... I'm sorry.
我不是想添麻烦
I... I... I don't mean to be a pain.
你没有  你只是被吓到了
You're not a pain. You're just scared.
要是我也会的
I would be, too.
她正在接受我们能给的最好的治疗
She's getting the best care possible,
一旦手术完成  我们就带你去见她
and as soon as we're done, we'll bring you to her.
谢谢
Thank you.
没事的
Okay.
你很擅长这种事
Y-you're... you're good at this.
下午2:52  值班7小时52分
蒙特奥医生请到术前准备室
Dr. Monteo to pre-op.
你不是在急诊室吗
Shouldn't you be in the ER?
莉亚不停给我打电话
Lea keeps calling me.
她想知道我为什么劝她回郝尔希镇
She wants to talk about why I told her to go back to Hershey.
你劝莉亚回郝尔希镇
You told Lea to go back to Hershey?
我以为这能解决问题  但我错了
I thought it would solve the problem, but no.
我错了  只会让情况更糟
No. It just made it worse.
她现在更加刨根问底
Now she wants to talk about it more,
但我已经无话可说了
but there's no more to be said.
人际关系不是这样维系的  肖恩
That's not the way it works, Shaun.
不能只是一个人单方面倾诉
It can't just be one person who does the talking.
你还要学会倾听
You have to listen, too.
我不想听她说这些
I don't want to listen to her.
太  难了
It's too...hard.
太难了
It's too hard.
维系人际关系本就不是易事
Well, relationships aren't always easy.
有时会变得复杂  麻烦
They get complicated, messy.
没错
Exactly.
所以我才不需要这些
That's why I don't want one.
你在说谎
Well, that's not true.
你能离开急诊室找我谈心
The reason that you left the ER to come talk to me
正因为我们是朋友
is because we have a relationship.
我们双方都能受益
And we both benefit from it.
莉亚是你的朋友
Lea's your friend.
你不能总是封闭自己
You can't just wall yourself off from people
以为这样就不会受到伤害
in the hope that you'll never get hurt.
封闭好  他就不会受到伤害
We need to wall it off so he doesn't get hurt.
保持冷静  伙计
Stay calm, buddy.
喉咙放松  用鼻腔呼吸
Just relax your throat and breathe through your nose.
钳子
Clamp.
-行了  -酷
- Got it. - Cool!
用力咬下去
Now bite down.
这是外科专用袋
This is a surgical pouch.
手术刀都切不开
It can't even be cut by a scalpel.
加油  你能做到
Come on, you can do it.
数到三
On the count of three.
一
One...
二
Two...
三
Three.
-伊内兹  -怎么了  他胆子太小了
- Inez! - What? He was being a total wuss.
闭嘴
Callate la boca!
好  厉害
That was...amazing.
你想在外浆膜和肌层之间
You want to create a plane between the outer serosa
造一面平面膜防止内腔受损
and muscularis layer to avoid disrupting the lumen.
跟她丈夫解释得还好吧
Everything go okay with the husband?
没事  然后  我想道歉
Yes. And, uh, I apologize.
我不该质疑你的决定
I shouldn't have questioned your decision.
没关系
It's all good.
两根病变的输卵管已切除  还剩一根
Two Fallopian lesions down, and one more to go.
你想来切除最后一根吗
You want to take the wheel on the next one?
好啊
Sure.
果然
Figures.
弗洛里斯护士  布朗医生执刀
Nurse Flores, do you have a problem
你有什么意见吗
with Dr. Browne taking the lead?
没有  只是觉得很有趣
No. I just find it interesting
你在她向你道歉后才给她执刀的机会
that you only gave her the opportunity after she apologized.
你可以刷手出去了
You can scrub out.
不  我不走
No. I'll stay.
这不是询问  我在命令你  刷手出去了
I'm not asking. I'm ordering. Scrub out.
不  我没有做错事
No. I've done nothing wrong.
你质疑了我在手术中的管理能力
You're undermining my management of this procedure.
因为我回答了你问的问题
By answering a question you asked me?
冷嘲热讽地质疑我的决定
By making snide comments questioning my judgment.
我不会离开岗位
I'm not leaving my post,
所以请继续工作吧
so why don't we just get back to work?
你  我还有安德鲁斯一会再好好谈谈
You, me, and Andrews will be discussing this later.
我很期待
I look forward to it.
下午4:37
需要更多的生理盐水
Gonna need more saline now!
你好  爸爸
Hi, Daddy.
下午4:37  值班9小时37分钟
你吃了吗
Have you eaten?
还没呢
N-not yet.
解决完这个我去吃午饭
I'll get lunch after I finish this.
午饭  都快5点了
Lunch? It's almost 5:00.
那就是晚饭
Then dinner.
我要去吃饭了  饿死了
Look, I'll go now. I'm starving.
半小时后回来
I'll be back in 30.
异常勃起的病人回来了[你勃起了]
Hey, your erection's back.
她说的不是我
She's not talking about me.
吊销驾照三十天并缴纳七百元罚款
30-day suspended sentence and a $700 fine.
把这些文件拿到306室
Take all these documents to Room 306.
亚历克斯·利昂先生
Mr. Alex Leon.
不行  法官阁下
No way, Your Honor.
我已经耐心等待很久了
I've been waiting patiently.
会轮到你的
We'll get to you.
什么时候  等到4点59你就可以说没时间了
When? At 4:59 so you can tell me you've run out of time
让我改天重来一次吗
and make me come back to do this all over again?
那就看看再说咯
Well, I guess we'll just have to see about that, won't we?
不  不行  坐下孩子
No, we won't. Take a seat, kid.
法官阁下  很抱歉我就接了两分钟电话
Your Honor, I am so sorry that my two-minute phone call
会造成如此大的不便
was such an incredible inconvenience,
但我是特意赶过来接受审理
but I went out of my way to be here today to have my case heard.
所以就审理我的案子吧
And that is exactly what I'm gonna do.
现在
Now.
请给我利姆医生的档案
Can I have Dr. Lim's file, please?
谢谢
Thank you.
我保证不会占用太多时间
And I promise this won't take long because,
请允许我解释
as I started to explain...
罪名成立
Guilty.
罚款一千五并吊销驾照一年
$1,500 fine and license suspension for one year.
在你走之前法警还有些文件
The bailiff will have some paperwork for you to sign
需要你去签字
on the way out.
你不能这么做
You can't do that.
我办公室有一大本厚书可以证明
I have a thick book in my office that says I can.
不  这是美国
No. This is America.
我交了税  你才有工资拿知道吗
I pay taxes, which pay your salary, by the way.
-别再往前走了  -我要找她评评理
- I wouldn't go there. - Oh, I am definitely going there.
我强烈建议你别再说了
I strongly advise you don't say another word.
你可以申请其他法官来裁决
You can appeal this verdict to a different judge.
我不需要其他法官
I don't want a different judge.
我要她做好她该死的工作
I want this one to do her damn job!
电话在前台
We keep the TP up front.
有需要就喊我们
Just give a yell if you need some.
晚上7:28  值班12小时28分钟
它会不会死掉
Is it gonna die?
放轻松  一切尽在掌握中
Just relax. Everything's under control.
你回答的不是「不会」
That's not a "No."
我们得看看化验结果  很快就回来
We're gonna review your lab results and we'll be right back.
等一下
Excuse me.
我们已经检查过化验结果了
We've already reviewed his labs.
没发现肿瘤细胞  镰状细胞
There's no sign of a malignancy, sickle cell,
淋巴瘤或白血病
lymphoma, or leukemia.
我知道  我需要点时间考虑
I know. I just need a minute to think.
-我们应该  -不行
- I think we should... - No.
不能给利姆医生打电话
We're not calling Lim.
我们已经被教训过一次了
We got our asses chewed out last time,
这也不是关乎生死的问题
and this is not life and death.
我们可以一小时每隔五分钟
We can inject diluted phenylephrine
注射一次稀释苯肾上腺素
every five minutes for an hour.
那他的阴茎里得注射不少液体
That's a lot of injections in his penis.
我会给他局部使用利多卡因
I'll give him a lidocaine local.
好吧  那就背神经麻醉
Fine. A dorsal nerve block.
你们男人真没用
You guys are such wimps.
那么多苯肾上腺素可能会导致高血压危象
That much phenylephrine could also cause a hypertensive crisis.
行吧  你就会说不  那你有什么主意
Okay, Dr. No, what's your idea, then?
你已经拒绝了
You already rejected it.
我们不打给利姆
We are not calling Lim.
你醒了吗
Are you awake?
是的
Yes.
如果一个患者有阴茎异常勃起
If a patient has reoccurring low-flow priapism
但是没有镰状细胞
but there's no sign of sickle cell,
血质不调或是霍金氏病的迹象
blood dyscrasia, or Hodgkins...
你问我干嘛  我是神经外科医生
Why are you asking me? I'm a neurosurgeon.
我是治这上面的  不是下面
My work is up here, not down there.
因为摩根不让我问
Because Morgan won't let me ask...
格拉斯曼医生
Dr. Glassman, why do you insist
你为什么坚持不听柯医生的医嘱
on ignoring Dr. Ko's medical advice?
我没有
I'm not.
是吗  她建议你在重症监护室病床上当顾问
Really? She advised you to do consults from your ICU bed?
我没让他过来
I didn't ask him to come in here.
睡觉吧
Go to sleep.
你以为呢  我熬了14小时零...
What do you think I've been trying to do for the last 14 hours
现在几点了
and... what time is it?
晚上8:17
8:17.
零47分
...47 minutes?
我需要更多吗啡和安比恩
I would like some more morphine, please, and an Ambien.
你知道你不可以的
You know you can't have either.
那我该怎么入睡
Well, then how the hell am I supposed to fall asleep?
我每次一翻身  都感觉要窒息了
Every time I turn, I strangle myself.
护士每三十分钟进来一次
You nurses come in here every 30 minutes
悄悄拿走我的体液
to steal my bodily fluids!
你有没有试过放松侧躺
Have you tried easing yourself onto your side
把枕头放在两腿之间
and putting a pillow between your legs?
当然了  所以问题出在这
Of course, that's the problem.
我怎么就不知道用枕头呢
I don't know how to use a pillow.
试试吧
Try it.
我会把灯全关掉
And I will turn the light all the way off,
莫菲医生会让你一个人待着
and Dr. Murphy will leave you alone.
温特疗法
Winter's procedure.
不能解决问题  但可以拖延时间
It's not the solution, but it'll buy you enough time
找到解决办法
to maybe find another one.
-谢谢  -不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
晚安  格拉斯曼医生
Good night, Dr. Glassman.
我们每清除一个病变处  又会再找到两处
Seems like for every lesion we excise, we find two more.
几点了
What time is it?
凌晨1:12
1:12 in the morning.
我的膀胱要炸了
And my bladder is about to burst.
切完这个以后  我要休息一会儿
After I finish this one, I'm gonna take a break.
我出去的时候  朴  你来接手
While I'm out, Park, you take over.
从我指给你看的膀胱上的那些病变开始
Start on the lesions I showed you on the bladder,
但是要小心
but be careful...
她的血压在下降
Her pressure's dropping.
她血流不止  看不见了
She's bleeding out. I can't see anything.
去拿内窥镜
We're taking out the scope.
得把她切开
We're gonna have to open her up.
我快速输注了两单位
I've got two units on the rapid infuser.
平均动脉压在六十左右
MAP is still hovering at 60.
动作快
Moving as fast as I can.
用洗必泰冲洗  但别胡乱冲洗
Paint her with Chlorhexidine and don't make it a Picasso.
-是用来应急的  -在做了
- It's a crash lap. - On it.
手术刀
knife.
流血控制住了
Uh, the bleeding's under control.
那她的膀胱怎么办
What about her bladder?
那里全是弥漫性病变
There's infiltrating lesions all over it.
连壁上都有
Even the walls are involved.
我们得把它切除了
We're gonna have to remove it.
然后给她安一个尿道口袋
And give her a urostomy bag?
肯定还有别的办法
There has to be another option.
如果我有别的办法
If I had another option,
弗洛里斯护士  我就说了
Nurse Flores, I would've suggested it.
如果我们把她的肠切除一部分
What if we excise part of her bowel,
用来重造她的膀胱呢
reconstruct a bladder?
那样比切除危险
That's a lot more dangerous than...
比让一个28岁的女人后半辈子
Making a 28-year-old woman urinate through a hole
都从一个腹部的洞排尿呢
in her abdomen for the rest of her life?
我觉得这个附加的危险是值得的
I think the additional risk is worth it.
看她丈夫同不同意吧
See if the husband agrees.
-行  我去  -不  朴去
- Okay. I'll go. - No, Park will.
他去问的时候  除了JL  布朗医生
And while he does, I want everyone but J.L., Dr. Browne,
和弗洛里斯护士  其他人都去清理手术室
and Nurse Flores to clear the OR.
你看着患者
You, monitor the patient.
你们俩  我们得谈谈
You two, we need to have a talk.
我有得选吗
Do I have a choice?
你想保留功能健全的阴茎吗
Do you want to keep a fully functioning penis?
-当然  -那就没得选
- Of course... - Then no.
这根比上次的还粗
That's even... Bigger than it was last time.
温特疗法需要加粗的针头
Winter's procedure requires an extra-large-gauge needle
来开一个足够大的洞以恢复血流
to poke a hole big enough to restore blood flow.
我们会用利多卡因给你做神经麻醉
We'll give you a lidocaine nerve block.
你什么都不会感觉到
You won't feel a thing.
上次为什么不给
W-why wasn't I given that last time?
上次还不值得冒险
The risk wasn't worth it before.
相信我  上次也值得
Uh, trust me, it was worth it before, too.
莉亚
我知道你晚上7点就值完班了
回我电话
好选择  我们马上回来
Good choice. We'll be right back.
你们不是说得马上做吗
W... You said that we needed to do this right now!
是的  我只是要和我的同事商量一下
We do. I just need to confer with my colleague for a moment.
凌晨2:13  值班20小时13分钟
你背着我和利姆说了
You're talking to Lim behind my back?
没有
No.
别说谎  你不擅长这个
Don't lie. You're not good at it.
我看见你删了她的信息
I saw you delete her text.
我知道不是格拉斯曼给你说用温特疗法的
I knew Glassman didn't give you the Winter's idea.
那条信息不是利姆医生发来的  是莉亚
The text wasn't from Dr. Lim. It was from Lea.
如果是莉亚发来的  为什么那么快删掉
If it was from Lea, then why'd you delete it so fast?
克莱尔说我不该把好朋友推开
Claire thinks I shouldn't push a good friend away,
但是一想到她
but thinking about her...
我不想跟她说话
I don't want to talk to her.
你不该听她们的
You shouldn't listen to them.
她们中任何一个
Either of them.
莉亚和克莱尔对你很好
Lea and Claire are nice to you.
但她们不是你的朋友
But...they're not your friends.
她们想照顾你  像照顾可爱的宠物
They want to take care of you, like a cute pet.
她们承认你是个好医生  但不把你当个男人
They take you seriously as a doctor but not as a man.
莉亚亲了我
Lea kissed me.
在我们唱完卡拉OK之后
After we sang karaoke.
肖恩  那是个怜悯的吻
Shaun, it was a pity kiss.
你没见过莉亚
You've never even met Lea.
没错
True.
但我知道她不是中学生
But I know that she's not in middle school,
那意味着  如果她把你当个男人
which means if she really thought of you as a man,
她就不会满足于一个纯洁的吻
she wouldn't have settled for just one innocent peck.
我只是
I just...
你在看什么
What're you looking at?
腓神经
坐骨神经
皮神经
肖恩
Hey, Shaun.
发生什么了  我以为在被传讯之前
What's going on? I thought I couldn't be released
都不会被释放了
until I was arraigned.
法官认为九小时是足够的惩罚了
The judge decided nine hours was enough punishment.
她才是该被惩罚的那个  我应该告她
She's the one who should be punished. I should sue her.
你该做的是学会闭嘴
What you should do is learn to keep your mouth shut.
我饿得没力气算你走运
You're lucky I'm hungry.
放下纷争
This stops now.
凌晨2:35
我们得共同合作
We need to work together.
在合作啊
We are.
之前一起想出了膀胱重建的想法
That's how we came up with the idea to rebuild her bladder.
你提出自己想法时
There's a way to offer your input
可以不用损害我的威信
without undermining my authority.
唯一损害你威信的是
The only thing that undermines your authority
你说布朗医生可能有经前综合征
is your comments about Dr. Browne's supposed PMS.
-什么  -我从没说过
- What? - I never said you had PMS.
我只是问朴知不知道
I just asked Park if he knew
你为什么比平常更易怒
why you were more irritable than usual.
我没有易怒  我可不是爱发牢骚的人
I'm not irritable, and I'm not a whiner!
我没说你是
I never said you were...
是你让我找安德鲁斯的  是你的主意
You told me to take it up with Andrews. This was your idea.
爱发牢骚的人是你才对
If anyone's a whiner, it's you.
够了
That's enough.
本来以为一小时能做完的手术
You're 12 hours into an operation
做了十二个小时还没完
you thought was gonna take one,
所以我大可以说
so I think it's safe to say
你们比平常都更易怒
you're all more irritable than usual.
但你们都得控制一下
But you need to get a grip.
梅伦德斯医生  你可能需要休息一下
Dr. Melendez, maybe it's time you took a little break.
吃点能量棒  喝点果汁
Get an energy bar and some juice.
我并不需要
I don't need a...
你需要
Do it anyway.
他回来后  你们都得在手术室就位
And when he gets back, I expect everyone in this OR
表现出你们的最佳专业素养
to conduct themselves with the utmost professionalism.
两份牛肉塔可
Can I get two brisket tacos, please?
凌晨2:48
不  要三份
You know what? Actually, make it three.
谢谢
Thank you.
你不守规矩
You're out of order!
她不守规矩
She's out of order!
整个交通法庭听证会都乱套了
This whole traffic court hearing is out of order!
好了  很好笑  机灵鬼
Okay, very funny, smart-ass.
我真的很敬佩你
Actually, I gotta give you props.
关于激光雷达校准那点你是对的
You were right about the LIDAR calibration.
要是你手机没响  你可能就不会被罚了
If your phone hadn't rung, you might've gotten off.
下次我会关机的
Next time, I will turn my phone off.
还下次  你都不能开车了
Next time? You're done.
结案了
Case closed.
你得开始努力刷高你的拼车评分了
You're gonna start having to work on upping your rideshare rating.
我肯定要起诉
I'm obviously gonna appeal.
她一开始就对我有偏见
She was biased against me from the start.
我一直都看到  掌权女人比男人差劲
I see it all the time... Women in power are worse than men.
不予置评
No comment.
牛肉塔可好了
Order up. Brisket tacos.
谢谢
Thanks.
谢谢你
Oh, thank you.
来一杯吗
Want one?
我也想喝啤酒  但是我不可以
I would love a beer. But I can't.
接下来的十七个小时我随时待命
I'm on call for the next 17 hours.
你还要随时待命
You're still on call?
要是你被关的时候有人找你怎么办
What would you have done if they needed you while you were locked up?
我大可以让他们打给值二线的医生
I would've had them phone my secondary coverage.
但我觉得没必要又吵醒一位医生
I didn't see the point in waking another doctor.
也没必要公开你的困境
Or publicizing your predicament.
我在争取升职
I'm competing for a promotion,
除非不得已  我不会让上司知道
and I didn't feel the need to tell my boss I was locked up
我被关的事情
unless I absolutely had to.
没有伤害就没有犯规
No harm, no foul.
她丈夫同意了
Husband consented.
你准备好了我们随时可以开始
We're good to go whenever you are.
刷手回手术室  我马上到
Scrub back in. I'll be right there.
我想杀了他们
Oh, I'm gonna kill them.
老天
Oh, God. Oh.
-不好意思  -没事
- Sorry. - It's okay.
什么事
What?
今早有个病人患有低血流阴茎异常勃起
We had a patient come in this morning with low-flow priapism.
凌晨4:28  值班21小时28分钟
我们以为是嗑药引起的
We thought it was drug-induced,
但是我又发现了他有足下垂
but then I noticed a foot drop...
说重点
Cut to the chase.
我们发现一处骨盆扩张硬膜外脓肿
We found an epidural abscess with pelvic extension and...
准备好手术  我十五分钟后到
Get him prepped. I'll be there in 15.
什么
What?
-我得走了  -不
- I gotta go. - No.
是病人有生命危险吗
Is someone dying?
我能及时赶到的话就不会有
Not if I can get there in time.
你能载我过去吗
Can you give me a ride?
用稀释的杆菌肽冲洗
Irrigate with diluted bacitracin.
摩根  冲洗
Morgan, irrigation.
不好意思  今天工作太久了
Sorry. It's been a long day.
你只有九个半小时
And you only have another nine and a half hours to go.
只剩九小时二十一分钟
Only 9 hours, 21 minutes.
布朗说得对  弹性工作制很荒谬
Browne's right. This flextime schedule is absurd.
是的  有缺点
Yeah, it has its drawbacks.
但如果交给下一班的人来做这个阴茎手术
But if this penis had been passed on to the next shift,
他们会以为你漏掉了什么环节
they would've assumed you missed something,
然后重新手术
and they would've done a whole new work-up.
耽误了可能会让他失去性功能
The delay could've paralyzed him.
但他们如果不是这么累
Or maybe they wouldn't be so tired
就能更早发现足下垂
and would've noticed the foot drop faster.
你们做得很好了
You guys are doing fine.
要习惯疲劳
And you'll get used to the fatigue.
一段时间后  就不会难受了
After a while, it won't even bother you.
你说起来简单
That's easy for you to say.
你这一整天都坐在沙发上等出诊电话
You were on home-call chilling on your couch all day.
说得好
Good point.
原位新膀胱放好了
Orthotopic neobladder is in place.
确定好排尿正常就继续
Let's make sure it drains properly before we move on.
血流通畅
Flow looks good.
等等  再往回推
Hold on, push it back again.
那是什么  子宫底部
What's that? At the base of the uterus?
看起来比较暗
It looks dusky.
再给我点染色剂
Can I get some more dye?
是一个多倍体肿瘤
It's a polyploid mass.
从子宫延伸到卵巢动脉
It extends from the uterine to the ovarian artery.
所有的侧支供血都被影响了
All collateral blood supplies have been invaded.
我们要切除整个子宫
We're gonna have to do a full hysterectomy.
如果我们切除肿瘤
What if we resect the mass
移植一条大隐静脉来搭桥呢
and graft a saphenous vein for bypass?
移植物闭塞的风险太大了  她会感染的
Risk of graft occlusion is too high. She'd go septic.
她最后跟我们说她一生的梦想是
The last thing she told us was her lifelong dream
做一名母亲
was to be a mother.
是个新点子  但
It's an innovative idea. But...
我们不能做决定
It's not our decision.
我出去和她丈夫谈
I'll scrub out and talk to the husband.
不  我去
No, I'll do it.
不  我不能替我妻子做这个确定
No, I... I... I can't make that decision for my wife.
不  你可以的
Yes, you can.
你已经做过一次决定了
You've already done it once.
这次不一样
This is different.
但这是吉娜希望的
But this is what Gina wants.
所以她才让你做她委托人
I... I... It's why she made you her proxy.
不  我做她委托人是因为
No. I'm... I'm her proxy because she didn't think
她认为不应该让她妈妈和姐妹们
she should ask her mother and sisters
为了一个小手术从缅因州飞过来
to fly from Maine for a minor surgery.
你必须得联系他们
Look, you have to call them.
不  吉娜选择了你
No, Gina chose you.
你才是那个熟悉她  真正理解她的人
You are the one who knows her, who truly understands her.
她希望我们做什么
What would she want us to do?
我不  我不知道
I don't... I don't know.
我是说  怎么会有任何人
I mean, how... how can any man...
拜托  告诉我该做什么
Please, just tell me what to do.
我昨天才遇到她  我几乎不认识她
I met her yesterday. I barely know her.
所以你才能有客观性  你才能做出正确的决定
So you can be objective. You... you can make the right call.
不  吉娜并不是要选一个客观的人
No, Gina didn't choose someone to be objective.
-他选择了你  -拜托告诉我怎么做
- She chose you. - Please, just tell me what to do.
-我不能  -你必须告诉我  因为我不会
- I can't. - You have to! Because I won't.
我不能那样对她
I can't do that to her.
拜托  帮帮我
Please. Just... just help me.
不管你叫我做什么  我都会做
Whatever you say, that's... that's what I'll do.
不管你说什么
Whatever you say.
你同情我吗
Do you feel sorry for me?
为什么
Why would I?
上午11:40  值班28小时40分钟
摩根说莉亚对我好
Morgan says Lea is only nice to me
只是因为她同情我
because she feels sorry for me.
摩根知道她为什么对你好吗
Does Morgan have a theory for why Morgan is so nice to you?
说实话  已经不仅仅是对你好了
I'm being honest, which is better than nice.
切掉这个纤维组织
Cut this fibrinous tissue.
双极止血钳
Bipolar.
有些女人把男人当做朋友
Some women put a guy in the friend zone
最后对待他更像宠物而非一个人
and they end up treating him more like a pet than a person.
摩根说的有道理  有些女人的确如此
Morgan has a point. Some women do that.
但只有跟莉亚谈谈才知道她是不是也那样
But the only way to find out if Lea does that is to talk to her.
伤口清理干净了
The wound is clean.
没有肉眼可见的感染
No more macroscopic signs of infection.
有脊椎神经损伤吗
Any spinal nerve damage?
在他醒来就知道了
Won't be able to tell until he wakes up.
中午12:21
他决定怎么做
What'd he decide?
他没有决定
He didn't.
他拒绝做出决定
He refused to make a decision.
他坚持让我替他决定
He, um, insisted that I do it for him.
她是真的很想成为母亲
She really wants to be a mom,
-所以我认为我们应该尽力  -不行
- so I think that we should try to... - No.
他选择让我来做这个决定
He chose me to make the decision.
她的生命比梦想更重要
Her life matters more than a dream.
做完整子宫切除
Do a full hysterectomy.
你说得对
You're right.
我们开始吧
Let's go.
她已经麻醉22小时了
She's already been under for 22 hours
我们还有很多活要干
and we got a lot more work to do.
精细组织剪和钳子
Metz and a forcep.
子宫骶韧带
E uterosacral ligament.
大号盘子
Large pan.
-时间  -4点10分
- Time? - 4:10.
她已经麻醉26小时10分钟了
She's been under 26 hours, 10 minutes.
好了  帮她缝合  然后叫她醒来
All right, let's close her up so we can wake her up.
我去通知她的丈夫
I'll go tell the husband.
不  让我去吧
No. I'll do it.
布朗医生  你来处理缝合
Dr. Browne, you take lead on the close.
动一下你的脚趾
Wiggle your toes.
每个脚趾都能动了
All 10 are going to market.
你很快就没事了
You're gonna be fine.
我的那个...
And, uh, w-what about my...
也会没事的
He'll be fine, too.
晚上6:13  值班35小时13分钟
谢谢你
Thank you.
别谢我
Oh, don't thank me.
这两位才是救了你的人
Those two are the ones who saved you.
靠他们自己
All on their own...
几乎
Almost.
发生什么了
What happened?
子宫内膜的病变比我们在影像上看到的
The endometrial lesions were much more invasive
更加严重
than we saw on the imaging.
为了清除所有病变  我们得在你的肠道外部
In order to remove them all, we needed to reconstruct
重建一个新的膀胱
a new bladder out of a section of your intestine.
所以我们得摘掉你的子宫
And we had to remove your uterus.
亲爱的  我很抱歉
Honey, I am so sorry.
会好起来的
It's gonna be okay.
我非常爱你
I love you so much.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
现在我们已经解决了手术危机
Now that we've handled the surgical crisis,
是时候处理不专业的行为了
it's time we deal with the unprofessional behavior.
我唯一的问题是  责任在谁
The only question I have is, who exactly is to blame?
一场27个小时的手术
It was a 27-hour surgery.
期间会有一些紧张的时刻
There were some tense moments.
但我很高兴看到
But I was very pleased with how everyone
大家最终一起完成了手术
ultimately worked together as a team.
我很钦佩布朗医生坚定不移地
I was especially impressed with how Dr. Browne
坚持她的立场
aggressively stood her ground and insisted
我也尊重丈夫对于妻子子宫切除手术的
that I respect the husband's final decisions
最后决定
regarding his wife's hysterectomy.
你们两个有什么想说的吗
Is there anything the two of you would like to share?
没有
No.
我没有
I'm good.
我想说
Well, I'd like to say...
梅伦德斯医生愿意倾听整个团队的意见
I was very impressed with Dr. Melendez's openness
这一点我非常敬佩
to hearing input from all of the surgical team.
这对我们护理人员来说
It's definitely something all of us
绝对是非常感激的
on the nursing staff appreciate.
非常好
Very good.
回家好好休息
Go home, get some rest.
B栋
你在这里
You're here.
是的  我在
Yeah, I am.
我不应该让你走的
I shouldn't have told you to go away.
这很不友好  而你对我一直都很好
It wasn't very nice and you've always been nice to me.
你是一个很好的朋友
You've been a good friend.
如果你想谈谈  我愿意听你说
If you want to talk, I will listen.
你说得对  我是一个很好的朋友
You're right. I have been a good friend.
实际上  我是一个非常棒的朋友
Actually, I've been an awesome friend,
但你是一个彻底的混蛋
but you have been a total jerk!
你就这么担心我伤害你吗
You are so worried about me hurting you?
那你是怎么伤害我的
What about how you hurt me?
怎么  你认为只有你才有感觉吗
What? You think you're the only one who has feelings?
你认为只有你才需要一个
You think you're the only one who needs someone
不会批判你  不会让你感到孤单的人
who doesn't judge them, doesn't make them feel totally alone,
世界上就没有一个人
like there's not one person in the world
真正关心他们的吗
who actually gives a damn about them?
好的  我很抱歉
Okay. I'm sorry.
不  你并没有
No, you're not!
你  你只是觉得不舒服
You're... you're just uncomfortable
你这样说只是想让我闭嘴
and you're trying to get me to shut up.
别担心  我会闭嘴
Which, don't worry, I will.
等我说完友情是双向的  我就闭嘴  肖恩
Just as soon as I finish telling you
that friendship is a two-way street, Shaun!
是双向的  你这个蠢货
A two-way street, you jackass!
我可能错了
Guess I was wrong.
她确实把你当一个真正的男人看
She does think of you like a real man.
晚上7:43
你醒了吗
Are you awake?
爸爸
Hi, Daddy.
曼蒂
Maddie?
你感觉如何
How are you feeling?
见到你真是太好了
It's so good to see you.
你死了
You're dead.
你以为我不知道吗
Don't you think I know that?
我死了吗
Am I dead?
没有  傻瓜  你只是累了
No, dummy. You're just tired.